http://www.berkeleynucleonics.com/privacy

Test and Measurement
Pulse & Delay Generators507 | 25 Amps Current Pulse Generator
508 | 6 Amps High Precision Current Pulse Generator
525 | Six Channel Portable Digital Pulse and Delay Generator
875 | 10MHz to 40GHz Vector Signal Generator
Microwave / RF Synthesizers825-M | 8kHz to 20GHz Ultra-Agile Signal Source
845-M | 20GHz RF / Microwave Synthesizer
865-M | 40GHz RF / Microwave Synthesizer
Multi-Channel RF / Microwave Signal Sources825-M-X | 8kHz to 20GHz Fast Switching Signal Source
845R | 2 Channel 10MHz to 20 GHz Synthesizer
845-M-X | 2 Channel 20 GHz
Synthesizer
855B | 300 kHz to 42 GHz Phase Coherent Signal Generator
865-M-X | Multi-channel 40 GHz Ultra-Low Phase Noise Synthesizer
Phase Noise Testers / Signal Source Analyzers7000 Series | 7GHz, 26GHz or 40GHz Phase Noise Tester
Radiation Detection
Isotope IdentifiersSAM 950 Ruggedized Isotope Identifier (RIID)
MetRad 1 Combined Metal and Gamma Radiation Detector
PM1621M Radiation Dosimeter (GM)
PM1703GN Gamma/Neutron Pager
PM1703M Gamma Radiation Pager
PM1703MO-1 PRD/Dosimeter Pager
Custom Scintillation Detectors Scintillation Crystals and Detectors
Compton Suppressors
BaF2 Barium Fluoride Scintillators for Fast Timing Measurements
YAP:Ce Scintillators for Fast X-Ray Spectroscopy
Online Training Scintillation Crystals and Detectors
CLLBC Scintillators High Resolution Gamma / Neutron Detectors
DSM-503 Digital Radiation Meter w/ Internal Detector
DSM-506 Digital Radiation Survey Meter w/ Internal/External Detectors
Privacy Policy
This statement explains our privacy and data protection practices.
It is important for Berkeley Nucleonics to safeguard its users' privacy while providing a personalized and valuable service. Collecting personal information is necessary if Berkeley Nucleonics is to satisfy the expectations and requirements of its registered users. It allows the Berkeley Nucleonics website to support our customers and colleagues with application-specific or product-specific support materials, quick access to our technical support, repairs and service, and sales departments.
The personal information you supply when registering at the Berkeley Nucleonics website will not be sold to any party outside the firm. The e-mail address you provide serves as your login and guarantees that you will have access to the most recent content relevant to your requirements. Your e-mail address is strictly protected at Berkeley Nucleonics, and any requests not to receive information via e-mail, fax, or direct mail are processed timely.
If you have additional questions or would like to be removed from the Berkeley Nucleonics website and service applications, please email info@berkeleynucleonics.com using your own email address.
Policy on "cookies" at Berkeley Nucleonics:
In addition to the personally identifiable information that you provide at the Berkeley Nucleonics website, anonymous information is collected using cookies. While cookies provide an important function in improving the usefulness of the internet, there is some confusion among internet users as to the appropriateness and usefulness of cookies. A cookie is a small text file containing a unique identification number that is transferred from a web site to the hard drive of your computer. This allows the web site to identify you and create a history of the pages you visit on the web site. This unique number identifies your browser, but not you, to the Berkeley Nucleonics website. All major institutions across all industries have implemented this simple technique on websites to better understand the traffic flow and usefulness of various sections of a website. However, a cookie does not provide any personally identifiable information such as your name and address.
Berkeley Nucleonics is not interested in the navigation of any one individual and does not collect personally identifiable information using cookies. Instead, Berkeley Nucleonics works to improve the usability of the website by reviewing statistical traffic analysis. These comprehensive reports indicate popular and useful materials vs insignificant webpages. Since cookies are only text files, they cannot run on your computer, search your computer for other information or transmit any information to anyone.
